websteronline.com 2018-10-31

# Privacy and Opt-Out Notice | Webster

**FACTS** | **WHAT DOES WEBSTER BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
---|---  
**Why?** | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
**What?** | The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and transaction history
  * account balances and payment history
  * credit history and credit scores

**How?** | All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Webster Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does Webster Bank share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes -** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes -**  
to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your creditworthiness | Yes | Yes  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**To limit our sharing** | 

  * Call [1-800-261-5482](tel:1-800-261-5482) toll free or [1-203-272-7711](tel:1-203-272-7711), or
  * Visit us online here.

**Please note:**  
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.  
---|---  
**Questions?** | Call [1-800-261-5482](tel:1-800-261-5482) toll free or [1-203-272-7711](tel:1-203-272-7711), or contact us.  
**Who we are**  
---  
**Who is providing this notice?** | Webster Financial Corporation and its family of companies: Webster Bank, N.A. (including its divisions: HSA Bank, Webster Investment Services, Webster Financial Advisors and its trade name Webster Private Bank); Webster Business Credit Corp.; Webster Capital Finance, Inc.; and Webster Wealth Advisors, Inc.  
**What we do**  
---  
**How does Webster Bank protect my personal information?** | To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
**How does Webster Bank collect my personal information?** | We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * open an account or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
  * pay your bills or apply for a loan
  * use your credit or debit card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?** | Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for information on your rights under state law.  
**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?** | Your choices will apply to you alone unless you tell us otherwise.  
**Definitions**  
---  
**Affiliates** | Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Our affiliates include financial companies with a common corporate indentity of Webster's name such as Webster Financial Corporation; Webster Bank, N.A.; Webster Business Credit Corp.; Webster Capital Finance, Inc. and Webster Wealth Advisors, Inc._

**Nonaffiliates** | Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Webster Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you._

**Joint marketing** | A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * _Our joint marketing partners include credit and debit card companies, broker-dealer companies, insurance companies and brokers, and financial services companies._

**Other important information**  
---  
**For Vermont Residents.** We will not share information we collect about Vermont residents with companies who are not affiliates, except as permitted by law, such as with your consent or to service your accounts. We will not share information about your creditworthiness with our affiliates without your authorization or consent, but we may share information about our transactions or experiences with you with our affiliates without your consent. You are not required to contact us for these elections to apply.  
**For California Residents.** We will not share information we collect about California residents with companies who are not affiliates, except as permitted by law, such as with your consent or to service your accounts. Among our affiliates, we will limit information sharing to the extent permitted by California law. You are not required to contact us for these elections to apply.
